Guide to the Gathering of the Tribes Archive 1983-2006 MSS.198
Fales Library and Special Collections
Gathering of the Tribes Archive
1983-2006
Fales Library and Special Collections
Gathering of the Tribes (Gallery)
MSS.198
20 Linear Feet (13 records cartons, 1 document case, 7 binders, 1 large oversize box)
The Gathering of the Tribes Archive includes correspondence, manuscripts, ephemera, photographic material, business and administrative records, video, audio, legal and financial records related to the operations of A Gathering of the Tribes, a literary magazine, gallery and performance space in New York's East Village.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Provenance
The Gathering of the Tribes Archive was purchased by NYU's Fales Library and Special Collections from Steve Cannon in 2007.
Related Materials
The Bob Holman Audio/Video Poetry Collection
The Ron Kolm Papers
Scope and Content
The Gathering of the Tribes Archive contains correspondence, manuscripts, ephemera, photographic material, business and administrative records, video, audio, legal and financial records. Materials in the archive document the operations of A Gathering of the Tribes, a literary magazine, gallery and performance space, and its publishing imprint, Fly By Night Press. The collection is arranged into seven series:
Series I: Media contains the audiovisual portion of the collection, inclusing video and audio cassettes.
Series II: Scrapbooks contains binders of material compiled by Tribes employees related to the gallery space, including ephemera, photographic material and event documentation.
Series III: Project Files contains files related to events, publications, and exhibitions, including correspondence, ephemera, artists' portfolios, and manuscripts.
Series IV: Grant Applications contains the records of all grant applications drafted by A Gathering of the Tribes.
Series VI: Publications contains printed material either published by, or associated with, A Gathering of the Tribes and Fly By Night Press.
Series VII: Data Storage contains electronic media, including compact discs and floppy discs.
Arrangement
The archive was arranged into six series based on the organization of items upon their arrival to the library. Archival materials were arranged at the folder level, alphabetically by folder title. Folder contents remain in the order in which they arrived at the library. Wherever possible, original folders were retained, numbered and described. Some folders were replaced due to preservation concerns. Materials that were too large for their original folders were rehoused in oversize boxes or into a map-case drawer. Audiovisual and media items were described at the item level. Scrapbooks were rehoused in archival binders for safe storage and access.
Historical Note
A Gathering of the Tribes is a literary magazine, gallery and performance space in New York's East Village. Founded in 1991 by Steve Cannon in his apartment, Tribes began as an informal salon for cultural exchange between poets, artists, musicians and performers. The collaborative, explorative work done in the space culminated in the founding of the Gathering of the Tribes magazine, whose first issue was published in the autumn of 1991. In 1993, part of the space became the Tribes Gallery, which plays host to exhibitions, readings, and performances.
Since its inception, A Gathering of the Tribes has sought to engage with and promote work from multi-cultural, interdisciplinary, and underrepresented writers and artists. Those featured at the gallery or published in the magazine include Ishmael Reed, Wynton Marsalis, Anyssa Kim, David Hammons, and Dora Espinoza. Tribes also publishes work under its Fly By Night Press imprint. Still in operation, Tribes remains a vibrant contributor to the East Village literary, artistic and performance scene alongside such venues as Nuyorican Poets Cafe and the Living Theatre.
Source:
"About." A Gathering of the Tribes. Web. 20 May 2014. http://www.tribes.org/web/about/.
For more information, please visit http://www.tribes.org.
Separated Materials
Four issues of A Gathering of the Tribes were removed from the archive to be catalogued. They can be found in the Fales Library's Downtown Collection, via Bobcat.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Audiovisual and born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
Grant proposals.; East Village (New York, N.Y.); Gathering of the tribes (Fly By Night Press); Scrapbooks.; Magazines (Periodicals); Publishers and publishing |z New York (State) |z New York |y 20th century.; Videocassettes.; Video recordings.; Poetry |x Slams.; Spoken word poetry; Nuyorican Poets Cafe; Kim, Anyssa; Parker, Charlie, 1920-1955; Cannon, Steve, 1950-; Marsalis, Wynton, 1961-; Gathering of the Tribes (Gallery); Reed, Ishmael, 1938-
- Series I: Media
  Scope and Content
  This series contains audiovisual materials related to A Gathering of the Tribes, many containing footage of poetry and jazz performances in the Tribes Gallery and elsewhere.
  Arrangement
  Items were given individual ID numbers and described at the item level. Titles are arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Subseries A: Video
    - Alice Zinnes: Tribes Production, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0017)
      Existence and Location of Copies
      Currently no access copy is available.
    - "All By Myself", Norman Loftis, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0251)
    - Allan Mazzini; Keychwa's Current Event Scratch, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotations: "Crank up the volume, please!"; "Please Excuse Sound Quality! It gets better as it moves on".; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0225)
    - America Becoming, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 01:30:00; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0155)
    - Amy Ouzoonian & Inez, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0137)
    - Angel Heart, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; No labels or annotations on cassette. Title transcribed from cassette sleeve. (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0023)
    - August 02/20th, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0227)
    - Big Guns / Bette Davis Interview / Bombshell (Harlow), circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0261)
    - Black News (Haiti) / Brown Sugar / New Orleans Now / L. King (Oprah Winfrey & Lisa Suarez / Blood Simple / M.V. Peebles [Bold Money] / Cat People, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Time-code information next to each title on cassette label.; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0189)
    - "Blight Spirit," Steve Cannon, Ishmael Cannon, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0130)
    - Bravo - Sugartown 8-10 / [Hamptons], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0301)
    - Butch Morris - Poets Choir at Whitney / Steve Cannon's Top of the World at Context, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0094)
    - Canada Trust TVC, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0003)
    - CBS / [M..] / M. Mono, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0262)
    - Ceci N'est Pas Un Peepshow, Cuns Interactabilis i.e., circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0259)
    - Censorship in the Press (Date and Participants Unknown), circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0304)
    - Channel 11 Newsreel, Harrison Willett, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0218)
    - Charlie Parker: Veritas Documentary, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0149)
    - Cheryl B Taylor - Tribes Open Mike, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0038)
    - Choreography Johons [Analhous], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0272)
    - (Class [...]), circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0297)
    - Closing Party (Poetry Reading) for Long Shot Magazine, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0319)
    - Coltrane / Jumeel Moon Doc and Dancers / October Blight, / Eleventh and B., circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Label annotations: "Video Void (Timing?)" (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0020)
    - Daniel Pollack, Writer/Director, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:08:00; Promotional "highlight reel" video.; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0231)
    - David Murray Big Band / Kansas City., circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0282)
    - Do the Right Thing, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 02:00:00; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0119)
    - Dominique Lowell: Women are Hungry, Sugar Daddy, When the Bitch Puts on Aretha You Know Theres Trouble (in 3 Parts), circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0084)
    - Edwin Torres / Sharon Mesner / Open Mike, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Sunday, April"; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0049)
    - Emile de Antonio: Painters Painting, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Commercial Release (Mystic Fire Video).; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0104)
    - Fashion Show / Oops, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0228)
    - Four Women, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS. (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0234)
    - Friday June 16th, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0311)
      DVD access copy available by appointment.
    - Gathering of the Tribes, Feb 15, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0174)
    - Groove, Bang & Jive Around, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0089)
    - Groove, Bang & Jive Around / Steve Cannon, St. Mark's Poetry Project, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0092)
    - Goussy's Birthday Party, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0167)
    - G.U.N. / Sex + Politics, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 00:24:20; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0205)
      Separated Materials
      A postcard flyer for "Shade: Plays by Franco & Melanie Maria Goodreaux" was removed from the cassette sleeve and can be found in Series.
    - Gunshot, by Individual Electric feat. Denis Giron; music: Central Park Drums & Los Papines, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:05:38; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0210)
    - Heaven & Hell - Return to Blowdryer!!, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0264)
    - High Society!, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0154)
    - Hubba City, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Handwritten label on cassette case: "Fragile Tape - View with Caution." (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0025)
    - Interns, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0308)
    - Ishmael Reed Interview, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0082)
    - [Ishmael] Reed Interview at Steve's, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0083)
    - Ishmael Reed: Savage Wilds, circa 1985-2007; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 00:30:00; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0004)
    - Jalla! Jalla!, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0235)
    - Jam Session at Tribes, Artist & Date unknown, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0278)
    - Jeronimo / Indians, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0022)
    - John and 3 Women (Part) / Milo's Peach / FreeUSA Raw Footage, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0103)
    - John Farris / Eileen Myles, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0125)
    - K. Kurismaa, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0106)
    - Keats / GBS / Major Barbara, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0195)
    - The Last Poem, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Label annotation: "Directed by Darran Sampson." (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0019)
    - Lee Liu & Tong, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Promotional release (Hot Shots, Cool Cuts).; Label information: "attn. Diane Paragis; MCI; Reel #1; Autumn Ftg.; Lightning Ftg."; Original Format: 3/4 in. Umatic. (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0232)
    - Live from NYC GO Poetry, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Label annotation: "Date and Place unknown". (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0283)
    - Lorenzo Pace, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0131)
    - Machito - A Latin Jazz Legacy / Carlos Ortiz - Nubia Music Society, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0186)
    - Maria Sentis, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0026)
    - Medellin - N.Y.: Juan Raul Hoyos: Kikis Ups / Londorio: The Parabol of the Fisherman, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0192)
    - Miguel's Reading, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0178)
    - Miles Davis - Unreleased!, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 01:18:00; Printed-out sleeve insert: "Miles Davis - West Germany 1967 & Berlin 1973", "Berlin - Philharmonie, 11/1/73", "Karlsruhe - Stadthalle, 11/7/67".; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0051)
    - My Fair Lady, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 02:50:00; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0194)
    - NASA Press Conference (Date Unknown), circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0303)
    - New / Music / Miles, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0018)
    - No Sucrose / Martha's "Mission of Love" at University of the Streets, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0096)
    - Nuyorican Poets Cafe: Short Poems / Poet's Choir "Butch Morris" / Slam - 6 Poets, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Nick Video"; "Short Poems - 14 mins.; Poet's Choir 'Butch Morris' - 45 mins."; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0123)
    - Ooh La La: Lina Pallotta, Steve Cannon, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0168)
    - The Oscars, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0091)
    - Personal Problems - Ishmael Reed, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Label annotation: "Reels 1 & 2 - 2-track audio". (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0270)
    - Planet Caravan, Episode 1, 2, 3, 7, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0191)
    - Planet Caravan, Episode 3, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0061)
    - The Poetry of Lester Afflick, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0006)
    - The Poetry of Lester Afflick, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Printed label: "Licensed for Private Viewing Only"; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0072)
    - Poetry Reading - Melenie, Hershel, Steve Dalan, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0136)
    - Poetry Reading: Michael Conroy Harris & Open Reading, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 01:10:00; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0169)
    - Poetry with Stephanie Agusto, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Label annotation: "Date Unknown" (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0276)
    - Police State, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0110)
    - Pops / Duke / Bird / Miles, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0115)
    - Prince - Live in N.Y.C., circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0129)
    - Racism Racism / In [D___], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0248)
    - Raw, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0179)
    - "Raw Fusion" Video Press Kit, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:20:00; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0182)
    - She Has Some [Hom__] (head), circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0247_a)
    - She Has Some [Hom__] (tail), circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0247_b)
    - Sheila Alson Memorial, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0138)
    - Smoking Word, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0053)
    - Star Black - Works on Papers @ the Tribes Gallery, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0005)
    - Steve Cannon, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: DVD (Box 9, Disk ID: 198.0321)
    - Steve Cannon, Edwin Torres and DJ Spooky, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Sticker label on cassette: "Magneticfilms.net"; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0105)
    - Sunday-Monday, July 10th / 11th, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0300)
    - Swedish Film Week, New York, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0233)
    - Teach Tolerance, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 00:22:00; Original Format: VHS; Label: "Office Copy, Southern Poverty Law Center" (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0298)
    - Tribes Gallery, Music Added, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0153)
    - Tribes Highlites, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 02:00:00; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0041)
    - Tribes Highlites, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotations: "Tribes' Steve Cannon"; "Video - By Nick Cirabisi"; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0060)
    - Tribes Productions / Alice Zinnes, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0164)
    - Tribes Production / Amy & Friends, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0240)
    - Two Iranian Poets, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0124)
    - [Unknown], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0013)
    - [Unknown], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0288)
    - [Unknown], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0289)
    - [Unknown], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0290)
    - [Unknown], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0309)
    - [Unknown], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0310)
    - Unusable, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0275)
    - Unusable, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0281)
    - Unusable, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0286)
    - VID #1, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0277)
    - Video Void #8, Studio [S_re], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0181)
    - Voo / Doo Movies, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0001)